voicemod.net 2019-05-21

# Voicemod Privacy Policy

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using or accessing our services (defined below), you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree with all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy and the applicable User Agreement, please exit, and do not access or use, our services.

  * Introduction
  * What Information we collect and how we use it
  * How and with whom we share personal data?
  * How you can access, update and remove your Personal Data

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of the General Conditions of Voicemod and will be applicable to personal data that users of the website www.voicemod.net, its SDK and its applications for Windows, Android and iOS provide to Voicemod , as well as those others who could communicate during the development of a contractual relationship with the company.

VOICEMOD assumes an active and committed compliance with the regulations on personal data protection.

The user, when providing the required information or personal data, is accepting their treatment and / or communication in the manner contemplated in this Privacy Policy.

VOICEMOD, as responsible for the data it collects from its users, has implemented in its computer systems and installations the necessary technical and organizational measures to guarantee its confidentiality and avoid its alteration, loss, treatment and / or unauthorized access. Likewise, VOICEMOD has proceeded to the registration of the corresponding files in the Spanish Agency for Data Protection.

## What Information we collect and how we use it

Voicemod collects Personal Data about you when you provide it directly to us, when third parties such as Payment Platforms provide us Personal Data about you, or when Personal Data about you is automatically collected in connection with your use of our services. We collect the following Personal Data from you:

### In our website (www.voicemod.net)

  * Contact Forms:  
In our website we have forms for you to contact us for support, feedback or to request more info about our services. We collect basic information to identify or contact you such as contact name and email address.

### In Funny Calls for iOS and Android

  *  **User Account Information:**  
Information that identifies you to the service, such as your mobile phone number, the IP address, the version of the operating system, the model of the terminal and your default language. We use the mobile phone number to authenticate you when you log in to the service and if you start a call, and use the IP address, the version of the operating system, the model of the terminal and your default language to help maintain your web session security while using the service.
  *  **Calls Information:**  
If you use this service to place calls, we collect information such as IP address, destination mobile phone number, network (wifi or 3G/4G), voice used to call and duration. We use this information to calculate the rate to apply depending on the destination and to analyze how users use the service.
  *  **Purchases within the app:**  
In the Funny Calls app for iOS we don’t participate in the purchase of credits to use in the App since the user makes the purchase through the App Store. The data that the user enters in the aforementioned process are subject to Apple's privacy policy, which you can consult at: <https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/es/terms.html#SERVICE>.

### In Another Voice for iOS

  *  **User Account Information:**    
Information that identifies you to the service, such as the version of the operating system, the model of the terminal and your default language. We use this information to authenticate you when you log in to the service, and to help maintain your web session security while using the service.

### In Voice Swap for iOS

  *  **User Account Information:**  
Information that identifies you to the service, such as the IP address, the version of the operating system, the model of the terminal and your default language. We use this information to authenticate you when you log in to the service, and use the IP address, the version of the operating system, the model of the terminal and your default language to help maintain your web session security while using the service.

### In Idiotify for iOS

  *  **User Account Information:**  
Information that identifies you to the service, such as the IP address, the version of the operating system, the model of the terminal and your default language. We use this information to authenticate you when you log in to the service, and to help maintain your web session security while using the service.

### In Voicemod SDK

  *  **User Account Information:**  
Information that identifies you to the service, such as contact name, email address, password, and IP address. We use this information to authenticate you when you log in to the service, and use the IP address to help maintain your web session security while using the service.
  *  **Financial Account Information:**  
In the case of payment customers we collect information needed to generate invoices; contact name, company name, address, city, state, post code, country and vat.

VOICEMOD does not store credit card data entered by users for the payment of their subscription; the indicated data are processed directly by the company responsible for the payment gateway, Stripe, to provide the service. Stripe is an American company that provides services to European companies through its subsidiary Stripe Payments Europe Limited, an entity located in Ireland and subject to European data protection regulations. You may consult Stripe's general privacy policy here: https://stripe.com/us/privacy. You may consult Stripe's policy regarding the transfer of data here: <https://support.stripe.com/questions/stripe-and-european-data-transfers>.

  *  **Final User of the service:**  
In the case of use of our software by third-party applications, VOICEMOD does not collect any personal data and only processes device identifiers and data used by the software to manage the licenses granted to third parties that in no case allow the users to be personally identified. In this case, the use of the functionalities provided by the VOICEMOD software will be subject to the privacy policy of the third parties that integrate it, without any intervention by VOICEMOD, for which in no case will it be responsible for the processing of the data carried out by such third parties.

### In Voicemod for Windows

  *  **User Account Information:**  
Information that identifies you to the service, such as the unique identifier of the computer, the version of the operating system and the email and the license key only for paid users. We use this information to authenticate you when you log in to the service, and to help maintain your web session security while using the service. For paid users, we use the email to send you the information about your License Key, communications about incidents or products and services of the Company.
  *  **Financial Account Information:**  
We don’t participate in the purchase process of the license, the user makes the purchase through Paddle.com. The data that the user enters in the aforementioned process are subject to the privacy policy of Paddle.com Market Limited, which you can consult at: <https://paddle.com/privacy>.
  *  **Transaction Information:**  
We receive information related to transactions made through paddle.com such as the product you have purchased, the email used to made the transaction, the currency of your country and the gross sale. We use all this information to validate your payment, to update your license status or to generate your new license key.

We also collect usage and performance information that is not Personal Data or that we aggregate it anonymously so that it no longer personally identifies you as an individual.

  *  **Unique Identifiers:**    
We use random unique identifiers as a customer ID to track individual usage behavior on our services. Unique identifiers collect information about a user’s use of our services on an individual basis.
  *  **Tracking Tools:**  
We and our third party service providers collect information about you, your device, and your use of the services through cookies and other tracking tools and technological methods (collectively, “Tracking Tools”). Tracking Tools collect information such as computer or device operating system type, IP address, browser type, browser language, mobile device ID, device hardware type, the website or application visited or used before or after accessing our services, the parts of the services accessed, the length of time spent on a page or using a feature, and access times for a webpage or feature. These Tracking Tools help us learn more about our users and analyze how users use the services, such as how often users visit our services, what features they use and what pages or views they visit. We also use Tracking tools to detect possible errors and corrections in the application and to evaluate the use and operation of new features within the services.

The Tracking Tools we are using in our services are:

    * GameAnalytics (<https://gameanalytics.com/privacy>).
    * Google Analytics / Fabric (<https://policies.google.com/privacy/update?hl=en>).
    * Facebook Pixel (<https://developers.facebook.com/docs/privacy/?locale=en_US>).

## How and with whom we share personal data?

We share Personal Data with third party service providers who work on our behalf and provide us with services related to all our services. These parties include:

  *  **Third parties** who act for us or provide services for us, such as billing and credit card payment processing, maintenance, sales, marketing, administration, support, data enrichment, hosting, and database management services.
  *  **Outside professional advisors** (such as lawyers and accountants) for purposes related to the operation of our business such as auditing, compliance, and corporate governance.

## How you can access, update and remove your Personal Data

At any time you can exercise your rights of access, rectification, opposition or cancellation by sending your request to [privacy@voicemod.net](mailto:privacy@voicemod.net) or via postal mail to Voicemod, SL, C / Obispo Don Jerónimo, 10 \- 46003 Valencia (Spain), Attaching a copy of your National Identity Document (DNI) or equivalent documentation.

Also, you can file a complaint with the Spanish Agency for Data Protection (AEPD), whose contact information is available through the website [www.aepd.es](https://www.aepd.es/).
